Stay down, pussy hole.
Nah.
I'm with you.
Let's hit him.
We won.
But this shit's just starting.
You done good out there, bruv.
Hello.
Liam, good to hear your voice, bro.
You too,
bro. I thought they were stopping your
calls.
They was. They filed a court order
to cut off contact with me on the outside.
Said I contribute to ongoing crime.
My lawyer got that shit struck down.
Now I get visitors.
I want you to come see me soon as you can.
I'm there, bruv.
You probably thought it was weird.
A huge fight,
and no one pulls a knife.
Truth is, we live under a code.
Years ago,
all crews made a deal with the pigs.
If we use fists, didn't kill,
and dealt nothing harder than weed,
they'd stay out of our business.
But the ambush at Southeast Croydon jarred
with the deal.
Trains, live tracks.
The fact no one was killed,
it was luck.
That's the danger if they win.
They might just decide they don't need
the deal if they've got an empire.
It's good to see you, man.
Shit's been lonely since you went down.
Good to see you too, bro. Lonely or not,
you've been leading from the front.
They gave me a private visiting room
'cause they were worried my brief would
go for costs.
But there's ears in here, too.
Viper probing your borders was him
testing
your defenses.
The ambush at East Croydon was him testing
your head for strategy.
He'll keep testing till he finds a weakness,
and he'll destroy it. It's what he does.
I don't know Can or Harrington too well,
but I know Viper better than anyone else
in this...
He ain't just a snake by name.
What's he gonna test next?
Your nerve.
He's gonna take the fight to you. Next
is a full frontal attack.
Listen, there's one thing we ain't talked
about.
Why are you here?
Assault, theft,
possession with intent to sell.
That's the shit I actually did.
You know what I mean.
Why are you here?
No. What do you mean?
Don't pull that thread,
bro. If you pull that thread,
you'll end up here with me.
And you've got a war to win.
Maybe I can help.
Leave it alone,
bro. That's an order.
Joe never told any of you about why he
went down, right?
Nah. No way one of the others would keep
it. No idea.
He told me not to look into it,
but fuck it. You got the best cop
connections.
See what you can find.